1. callTestCase(findTestCase("tCC Components/tCC tA Open For Edit"), ["$username":"", "$password":"", "$origQuote":"", "$newOrigQuote":""], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. callTestCase(findTestCase("tCC Components/tCC Login"), ["user":$username, "password":$password], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. if (openBrowser)
1. openBrowser("")
5. maximizeWindow()
5. println("Opening " + url)
9. navigateToUrl(url)
13. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/text_tCCVersion"), 30)
17. version = getText(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/text_tCCVersion"))
21. version = version
25. println("Version is " + version)
29. if (user == "")
1. println("Logging in as " + user1Name)
5. setText(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/input__username"), user1Name)
9. setText(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/input__password"), user1Password)
13. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/button_Login"))
5. if (callTestCase(findTestCase("tCC Components/tCC Select Org-Lang-Resource"), ["organization":"", "language":"", "resource":"unfoldingWord® Translation Academy"], STOP_ON_FAILURE) == false)
1. if (organization == "")
1. organization = organization
5. if (language == "")
1. language = langCode
9. println("Choosing organization " + organization)
13. if (waitForElementPresent(organization, 5, OPTIONAL) == false)
2. click(organization)
6. alerted = waitForAlert(2)
10. if (alerted == true)
2. println("Not alerted on organization")
6. alertFlag = false
10. println("Choosing resource " + resource)
14. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/resource_Parmed", ["resource":resource]))
18. println("Choosing language " + language)
22. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/combo_Select Language"))
26. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/listOption_Language_Parmed", ["lang_code":language]))
14. return true
9. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/span_translate"))
13. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/span_bita-humanbehavior"))
17. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/span_01.md"))
5. click(findTestObject("Page_tCC translationAcademy/section_BentOver"))
9. click(findTestObject("Page_tCC translationAcademy/text_BentOver"))
13. click(findTestObject("Page_tCC translationAcademy/header_BentOver"))
17. delay(2)
21. if (!(getText(findTestObject("Page_tCC translationAcademy/text_BentOver")).contains("Yahweh")))
2. println("Block quote text is correct")
6. if (!(verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Page_tCC translationAcademy/button_SaveEnabled"), 1, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)))
1. unfoldingWord_Keywords.SendMessage.SendFailMessage("Test failed because the Save button was not enabled after text change.")
5. click(findTestObject("Page_tCC translationAcademy/text_BentOver"))
9. sendKeys(findTestObject("Page_tCC translationAcademy/text_BentOver"), Keys.chord(END))
13. sendKeys(findTestObject("Page_tCC translationAcademy/text_BentOver"), "x")
17. click(findTestObject("Page_tCC translationAcademy/header_BentOver"))
21. delay(2)
25. click(findTestObject("Page_tCC translationAcademy/button_SaveEnabled"))
29. waitForElementNotPresent(findTestObject("Page_tCC translationAcademy/button_SaveEnabled"), 30)
33. click(findTestObject("Page_tCC translationAcademy/text_BentOver"))
37. sendKeys(findTestObject("Page_tCC translationAcademy/text_BentOver"), Keys.chord(END))
41. sendKeys(findTestObject("Page_tCC translationAcademy/text_BentOver"), Keys.chord(BACK_SPACE))
45. click(findTestObject("Page_tCC translationAcademy/header_BentOver"))
49. delay(2)
10. click(findTestObject("Page_tCC translationAcademy/button_SaveEnabled"))
14. if (!(waitForElementNotPresent(findTestObject("Page_tCC translationAcademy/button_SaveEnabled"), 30)))
25. closeBrowser()
1. separator = "==========================================================================================================================="
5. println(separator)
9. prefix = " +++++++++++ "
13. if (testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus() != "PASSED")
1. prefix = " ---------------------- "
17. println(prefix + testCaseContext.getTestCaseId() + " on " + version + " " + testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus() + prefix)
21. tsMessages.add("##" + testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
25. if (tcMessages.size() > 0)
1. for (def i : (0..(internal.GlobalVariable.tcMessages.size() - 1)))
1. println(tcMessages[i])
5. tsMessages.add(tcMessages[i])
29. println(separator)
1. tcMessages = []
5. executionProfile = getExecutionProfile()
9. logInfo("Execution profile is " + executionProfile)