25. println("setup success")
1. openBrowser("www.google.com")
5. println("this is a failing test")
9. unfoldingWord_Keywords.SendMessage.SendFailMessage("Failing test was run")
13. closeBrowser()
17. scriptRunning = false
1. suite = false
5. fileName = testSuiteLogFile
9. if (fileName.length() > 1)
1. suite = true
5. println("test case teardown in suite")
9. println("define file")
13. oFile = new java.io.File(fileName)
17. println("before append to file")
21. oFile.append("this is a log file
")
25. println("after append")
29. println("open log file at " + fileName)
13. browser = unfoldingWord_Keywords.GetTestingConfig.getBrowserAndVersion()
17. separator = "==================================================================================================================================================="
21. msg = separator
25. println(msg)
29. if (suite)
1. println("before file append 2")
5. oFile = new java.io.File(fileName)
9. oFile.append(msg + "
")
13. println("after file append 2")
33. prefix = " +++++++++++ "
37. testCaseStatus = testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus()
41. if (scriptRunning)
45. if (testCaseStatus != "PASSED")
1. prefix = " ---------------------- "
49. msg = prefix + testCaseContext.getTestCaseId() + " on " + version + " running on " + browser + " " + testCaseStatus + prefix
53. println(msg)
57. if (suite)
1. oFile = new java.io.File(fileName)
5. oFile.append(msg + "
")
61. tsMessages.add("##" + testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
65. if (tcMessages.size() > 0)
1. for (def i : (0..(internal.GlobalVariable.tcMessages.size() - 1)))
1. println(tcMessages[i])
5. tsMessages.add(tcMessages[i])
69. if (scriptRunning)
73. if (testCount > 0)
77. println(separator)
81. if (suite)
1. oFile = new java.io.File(fileName)
5. oFile.append(msg + "
")
1. msg = ""
5. separator = "vvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvv"
9. println(separator)
13. prefix = ">>>>>>>>>"
17. hdr = false
21. first = true
25. error = false
29. for (def i : (0..(internal.GlobalVariable.tsMessages.size() - 1)))
1. if (tsMessages[i] != null && tsMessages[i].length() > 2)
1. if (tsMessages[i][(0..1)] == "##")
1. if (!(first))
5. msg = prefix + tsMessages[i][(2..(internal.GlobalVariable.tsMessages[i].length() - 1))]
9. println(msg)
13. hdr = true
17. first = false
1. if (tsMessages[i] != null && tsMessages[i].length() > 2)
1. if (tsMessages[i][(0..1)] == "##")
1. if (!(first))
1. if (hdr)
1. if (!(error))
1. msg = "+++++++++++++++++++ PASSED +++++++++++++++++++++"
5. println(msg)
9. error = false
5. if (error)
9. msg = "
----------------------------------------
"
13. println(msg)
5. msg = prefix + tsMessages[i][(2..(internal.GlobalVariable.tsMessages[i].length() - 1))]
9. println(msg)
13. hdr = true
17. first = false
1. if (tsMessages[i] != null && tsMessages[i].length() > 2)
1. if (tsMessages[i][(0..1)] == "##")
2. msg = tsMessages[i]
6. println(msg)
10. hdr = false
14. error = true
33. if (error)
1. msg = "******************* FAILED *********************"
5. println(msg)
9. error = false
37. if (hdr && !(error))
41. msg = "^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^"