1. callTestCase(findTestCase("tCC Components/tCC tA Open For Edit"), ["$username":"", "$password":"", "$origQuote":"", "$newOrigQuote":""], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. callTestCase(findTestCase("tCC Components/tCC Login"), ["user":$username, "password":$password, "newSession":true], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. if (newSession)
1. if (openBrowser)
1. openBrowser("")
5. maximizeWindow()
5. println("Opening " + url)
9. navigateToUrl(url)
13. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/text_tCCVersion"), 30)
17. version = getText(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/text_tCCVersion"))
21. version = version
25. println("Version is " + version)
5. if (user == "")
1. println("Logging in as " + user1Name)
5. setText(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/input__username"), user1Name)
9. setText(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/input__password"), user1Password)
13. if (verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/button_Login"), 1, OPTIONAL))
1. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/button_Login"))
5. if (callTestCase(findTestCase("tCC Components/tCC Select Org-Lang-Resource"), ["organization":"", "language":"", "resource":"unfoldingWord® Translation Academy"], STOP_ON_FAILURE) == false)
1. if (organization == "")
1. organization = organization
5. if (language == "")
1. language = langCode
9. println("Choosing organization " + organization)
13. if (waitForElementPresent(organization, 5, OPTIONAL) == false)
2. click(organization)
6. alerted = waitForAlert(2)
10. if (alerted == true)
2. println("Not alerted on organization")
6. alertFlag = false
10. println("Choosing resource " + resource)
14. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/resource_Parmed", ["resource":resource]))
18. println("Choosing language " + language)
22. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/combo_Select Language"))
26. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/listOption_Language_Parmed", ["lang_code":language]))
14. return true
9. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/span_translate"))
13. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/span_bita-humanbehavior"))
17. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/span_01.md"))
5. click(findTestObject("Page_tCC translationAcademy/section_BentOver"))
9. click(findTestObject("Page_tCC translationAcademy/text_BentOver"))
13. click(findTestObject("Page_tCC translationAcademy/header_BentOver"))
17. if (!(getText(findTestObject("Page_tCC translationAcademy/text_BentOver")).contains("Yahweh")))
2. println("Block quote text is correct")
21. if (unfoldingWord_Keywords.TestVersion.isVersionGreater("1.0.4"))
1. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/button_Preview"))
5. click(findTestObject("Page_tCC translationAcademy/section_Having BIRTH PAINS"))
9. elementBirthPains = "Page_tCC translationAcademy/blockquote_Be in pain and labor"
13. sendKeys(findTestObject(elementBirthPains), Keys.chord(COMMAND, DOWN))
17. sendKeys(findTestObject(elementBirthPains), Keys.chord(SPACE))
21. delay(1)
25. if (getText(findTestObject(elementBirthPains)).contains("&gt;"))
2. try
1. sendKeys(findTestObject(elementBirthPains), Keys.chord(ENTER), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
5. sendKeys(findTestObject(elementBirthPains), "> This is line 1", STOP_ON_FAILURE)
9. sendKeys(findTestObject(elementBirthPains), Keys.chord(ENTER), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
13. sendKeys(findTestObject(elementBirthPains), "> This is line 2", CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
6. click(findTestObject("Page_tC Create/button_preview"))
10. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Page_tCC translationAcademy/paragraph_My little children"), 2)
14. bText = getText(findTestObject("Page_tCC translationAcademy/paragraph_My little children"))
18. lf = 10
22. eText = "ULT)" + lf + "This is line 1" + lf + "This is line 2"
26. if (!(bText.contains(eText)))
2. println("Line feeds were correctly included in block quotes")
25. println("Testing for sections visible and invisible")
29. println("Showing sections")
33. delay(1)
37. click(findTestObject("Page_tCC translationAcademy/button_Sections"))
41. if (!(verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Page_tCC translationAcademy/text_BentOver"))))
2. println("tA text for "Bent over" is visible when sections are open")
45. if (!(verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Page_tCC translationAcademy/text_Be in pain and labor to give birth"))))
2. println("tA text for "Be in pain and labor" is visible when sections are open")
49. println("Hiding sections")
53. scrollToPosition(0, 0)
57. delay(2)
61. click(findTestObject("Page_tCC translationAcademy/button_Sections"))
65. if (!(verifyElementNotVisible(findTestObject("Page_tCC translationAcademy/text_BentOver"))))
2. println("tA text for "Bent over" is not visible when sections are closed as expected")
69. present = verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Page_tCC translationAcademy/text_Be in pain and labor to give birth"), 1, OPTIONAL)
73. if (present && !(verifyElementNotVisible(findTestObject("Page_tCC translationAcademy/text_Be in pain and labor to give birth"), OPTIONAL)))
2. println("tA text for "Be in pain and labor" is not visible when sections are closed as expected")
77. println("Testing for sections and blocks visible")
81. println("Showing sections and blocks")
85. click(findTestObject("Page_tCC translationAcademy/button_Sections"))
89. click(findTestObject("Page_tCC translationAcademy/button_Blocks"))
93. delay(1)
97. if (!(waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Page_tCC translationAcademy/text_BentOver"), 1, OPTIONAL)) || !(waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Page_tCC translationAcademy/text_Be in pain and labor to give birth"), 1, OPTIONAL)))
2. println("tA text is visible with Sections and Blocks open as expected")
101. scriptRunning = false
105. closeBrowser()
1. suite = false
5. fileName = testSuiteLogFile
9. if (fileName.length() > 1)
1. suite = true
5. println("test case teardown in suite")
9. println("log file is at " + fileName)
13. browser = unfoldingWord_Keywords.GetTestingConfig.getBrowserAndVersion()
17. separator = "==================================================================================================================================================="
21. msg = separator
25. println(msg)
29. if (suite)
1. oFile = new java.io.File(fileName)
5. oFile.append(msg + "
")
33. prefix = " +++++++++++ "
37. testCaseStatus = testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus()
41. if (scriptRunning)
45. if (testCaseStatus != "PASSED")
49. msg = prefix + testCaseContext.getTestCaseId() + " on " + version + " running on " + browser + " " + testCaseStatus + prefix
53. println(msg)
57. if (suite)
1. oFile = new java.io.File(fileName)
5. oFile.append(msg + "
")
61. tsMessages.add("##" + testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
65. if (scriptRunning)
69. if (tcMessages.size() > 0)
73. if (scriptRunning && 1 == 2)
77. if (testCount > 0)
81. msg = separator
85. println(msg)
89. if (suite)
1. oFile = new java.io.File(fileName)
5. oFile.append(msg + "
")
1. msg = ""
5. separator = "vvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvv"
9. println(separator)
13. prefix = ">>>>>>>>>"
17. hdr = false
21. first = true
25. error = false
29. for (def i : (0..(internal.GlobalVariable.tsMessages.size() - 1)))
1. if (tsMessages[i] != null && tsMessages[i].length() > 2)
1. if (tsMessages[i][(0..1)] == "##")
1. if (!(first))
5. msg = prefix + tsMessages[i][(2..(internal.GlobalVariable.tsMessages[i].length() - 1))]
9. println(msg)
13. hdr = true
17. first = false
33. if (error)
37. if (hdr && !(error))
1. msg = "+++++++++++++++++++ PASSED +++++++++++++++++++++"
5. println(msg)
41. msg = "^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^"
45. println(msg)